<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 09:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ 1.1.0 released!</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.1.0/
            </link>
            <description>
                We are very pleased to announce the 1.1.0 release of Quarkus Tools for IntelliJ. This release brings support for YAML configuration files and bug fixes. application.yaml support Code completion (Ctrl + ENTER) Property documentation Select a property and press Ctrl+Q Syntax validation Wrong property key names or values are reported...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/intellij-quarkus-tools-1.1.0/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.8 released - Multiple Persistence Units, Micrometer, jbang, GraalVM 20.2</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-8-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                We have been hard at work during Summer to bake Quarkus 1.8. It comes with some shiny new features, among them: Multiple persistence units support for the Hibernate ORM extension A new Micrometer extension jbang integration for easy Quarkus-based scripting An update to GraalVM 20.2 As usual, it also comes...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-8-0-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Handling paginated APIs with Mutiny</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mutiny-pagination/
            </link>
            <description>
                At the beginning of the Mutiny adventure, my friend Alex came to me with an interesting problem. Alex wanted to retrieve data from a REST service in a reactive manner. So far, no problem, we have everything for this in our toolbox. But, this service, as many services, is using...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mutiny-pagination/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Wipro Addresses Seismic Shift in Retail with Quarkus</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/wipro-customer-story/
            </link>
            <description>
                Retailers are aggressively adopting cloud technologies to keep up with changing customer needs, seasonal demands, and increased competition. Digital retailers, like Amazon, are disrupting the industry and retailers are looking for ways to remain competitive through technology. Retailers are making significant investments in the acquisition and adoption of cloud software...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/wipro-customer-story/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.7.3.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-7-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.7.3.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.7.0.Final, 1.7.1.Final or 1.7.2.Final. What&#8217;s new? This release is a maintenance release that fixes various bugs found in 1.7.2.Final and provides some documentation updates. Thanks to our contributors, we also made...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-7-3-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Combining Apache Kafka and the Rest client</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kafka-rest-client/
            </link>
            <description>
                Another week, another interesting question. This week, someone asks me about combining Kafka and the Rest Client. That is a recurring subject, and most of the time, the goal is to achieve the following process: In other words, we want to call a remote service for each Kafka message we...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/kafka-rest-client/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.7.2.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-7-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.7.2.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.7.0.Final or 1.7.1.Final. What&#8217;s new? This release is a maintenance release that fixes various bugs found in 1.7.1.Final and provides some documentation updates. You can get the full changelog of 1.7.2.Final...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-7-2-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using Redis with Mutiny - Composing asynchronous actions</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mutiny-redis/
            </link>
            <description>
                I got an interesting question from a user about Redis and Mutiny. While the problem was not specifically about Redis and could be applied to many other APIs, I found the context amusing. Enrico, the user, wanted to do something like this: 1. get all keys from Redis 2. for...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/mutiny-redis/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Hackathon Winners</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-hackathon-winners-announced/
            </link>
            <description>
                Congratulations to the Winners The winners of the Supersonic, Subatomic Java Hackathon were announced on Friday during a “live judging” session. The submissions greatly exceeded expectations and the process of selecting the winners was difficult. Best Overall ($10,000) Slurpanize Best Serverless ($5,000) BrightAct Against Domestic Violence Best Kubernetes-native ($5,000) Slurpanize...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-hackathon-winners-announced/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 1.7.1.Final released - Bugfixes</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-7-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 1.7.1.Final with some bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for everyone using 1.7.0.Final. What&#8217;s new? This release is a maintenance release that fixes various bugs found in 1.7.0.Final and provides some documentation updates. Thanks to our contributors, we also made numerous improvements to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-1-7-1-final-released/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
